THE ORDINARY JACKPOT
Sometimes, I get so caught up working
and end up alone in the office.
When that happens
part of me wants to leave
as soon as I can
while another part of me
feels proud of working hard.
I even fool myself into thinking
I'm the most important person
in the company.
I have 1.3 billion won.
But that's not enough to quit my job
or completely change my life.
I can't decide what to do
with the money.
So I continue going to work.
In the meantime,
while I'm stuck in indecision...
someone else is taking
the biggest leap of their life.
RESIGNATION LETTER
JEONG SEON-HYUK
If you want a raise or more benefits,
or if the work is too tough
just say so
instead of pulling a stunt like this.
It's not that.
I'm really planning to leave.
Isn't your kid starting school soon?
Can you afford to quit?
Yes, we'll be fine for now.
What brought this on all of a sudden?
Honestly, didn't you
see this coming, Ms. Park?
If I try to make a move
it feels like I'm getting in the way
of the others' promotions.
But if I do nothing
it feels like I'm holding back
the newer, younger employees.
Mr. Jeong, you are so...
Pathetic, aren't I?
Trust me, I know.
I know that
but once I took a passive approach
it was hard to break out of it.
So I'm trying to change
my environment instead.
Starting your own business?
I won't make you sign
a non-compete agreement
so be honest with me.
EPISODE 4:
MUTUAL CAUSE, MUTUAL EFFECT
- Hello, Ju-hui.
- Hello.
Come on, get to work on time.
A team leader shouldn't be last.
Right, my apologies.
You've been
exactly 13 minutes late lately.
Going to the gym?
I had something to take care of.
We all have our own things going on.
That's an excuse for a rookie,
not a team leader.
I'm sorry.
And where's Mr. Jeong?
Even if he's quitting,
he should still get here on time.
Isn't that common courtesy?
He said he was going
to stop by the mall today
to say his goodbyes.
Everyone's just doing
whatever they want.
Is this a playground?
A train station?
How ridiculous.
All right, let's start the meeting.
We have a lot to go over.
Gi-tae, when are you going
to the mall?
I'll head over right after lunch.
They need to finish construction
this week
so keep morale up,
but keep the pressure on too.
Got it.
Also, tonight at 8 p.m.
You remember, correct?
Yes.
6TH FLOOR SALES DIVISION 1
Assistant Manager Jang Hyang-eun
will join our team next week.
But she's already here.
Pardon?
Hello, Mr. Gong.
Oh, hello, Ms. Jang.
What brings you here?
I came to say hello
and meet our business partners.
Have you been well?
Yes, it's been a long time.
Right.
Hello, Mr. Yang.
Wow, long time no see.
I look forward to working with you.
Likewise.
You haven't met these two yet,
have you?
- This is...
- Gi-tae?
Hello, ma'am.
I've heard a lot about you.
All good things, I hope.
Yes, of course.
And you're Ji-hye?
I look forward
to working with you, ma'am.
- Are you managing the center?
- Yes.
Can I ask you a favor?
Of course, anything.
I'd like the following information
by my first official day.
Baseline margins for the brands
Team 5 is in charge of.
Customer prices.
Each brand's customer service manual.
Credit memo logs.
Invoice checklists.
Total penalty points.
Direct numbers for all brand reps
as well as their email addresses.
Can you put that together for me?
Baseline margins, customer prices...
Customer service manuals.
I'd be disappointed
if I had to repeat myself.
I'll say hello to Ms. Park.
That's Ms. Jang.
She was always good at her job, no?
She hasn't changed a bit.
Is this right?
Will Ji-hye and I be okay?
Of course not.
You're screwed.
DAILY ROUTINE
Thank you.
I didn't know there was
a spot like this nearby.
Most of our colleagues don't know.
I stop by every morning before work.
So you called me to ask
about Jang Hyang-eun, right?
Yeah, she's joining my team,
so I need to know more about her.
I told you all I know last time.
Something happened
while she was at the China branch.
But they kept a tight lid on it,
so no one knows the details.
They froze all personnel transfers,
but she managed to return to Korea.
That's everything.
So you don't actually know anything.
I don't.
But nothing good will come
from getting involved with her.
Whatever she did while she was there
it'll only make it harder
to work with the China branch.
All right, then.
I'm sure she'll tell me
when she's ready.
That's a good mindset.
Just take it easy.
All you need to think about is
how to utilize your team members.
Ms. Jang should take over
the center now.
I said, think about it.
Really think it through.
What about Lee Ji-hye?
She's only a contract worker,
so she must be anxious already.
And now this woman flies in
from China and takes her spot?
How do you think she'd feel?
Even so, work is work.
You're so cold-blooded.
Don't you have any empathy?
What about you?
You claim to be such an empath.
But why don't you empathize with me?
You sure have a way with words.
Anyway, keep doing your job
but don't forget to look out
for your team, Mr. Gong.
I got this for you.
Try it. It'll bring out your empathy.
It's good.
See, I told you.
Hello, Mr. Yang.
I just arrived at the store.
Sure, I'll send you a photo.
All right.
VITAMIN ENERGY DRINK
Okay.
Hello, sir.
Thank you for your hard work.
Hey, get off me.
I'm already hot as it is.
My goodness.
Construction is practically done.
Done, my foot.
We've got a long way to go.
We worked until 2 a.m. last night.
Don't give us last-minute orders.
You always cut it close.
Come on now.
Have a drink, sir.
- Fine.
- All right.
Have a drink while you work.
Here you go.
Thank you for your hard work.
Gosh, it's so dusty in here.
This just won't do.
Hi, is this General Affairs?
I'm calling from the Laknes store.
Can you send someone to vacuum?
Sorry?
You should know
where the Laknes store is by now.
Do you have any idea
how hard these people are working?
Yes, please be more considerate.
Thank you in advance.
- Jeez.
- Goodness.
You Hongsung people, I swear...
So should we start
the electrical work?
You're the best.
We're counting on you.
Whatever.
Let's start on electrical.
We can follow the blueprint.
All right, let's see.
Since this is a clothing store...
- These aren't heavy at all.
- Just leave them. We'll handle it.
It's the least I can do.
Light as a feather.
- Hey, Gi-tae.
- Hello, Mr. Yang.
Construction is going well.
They're cleaning up now.
Okay, good work.
Are you coming back now?
Oh, since I'm here
I figured I'd make my rounds
at the other stores.
Good idea. But don't go empty-handed.
Buy them something to drink.
Understood, sir.
I'll see you later, then.
All right. Good work.
Gi-tae's gotten pretty savvy.
- It looks too cramped, doesn't it?
- Yes.
It might fall off the edge.
How about this...
I think it's okay now.
Over here, Mr. Jeong.
Were you checking on construction?
Yes.
Have a seat.
Did you make your rounds?
Yes, I said hello
to everyone at the office.
How does it feel to be back?
It's great, of course.
A bit awkward too.
You must have a lot on your mind.
I'm not entirely at ease.
It wasn't an easy decision
for me, either.
I wasn't sure taking you in
was the right call.
I completely understand
where you're coming from.
Let me be clear.
Just because I approved it
doesn't mean I was happy about it.
Yes, ma'am.
The audit of the China branch
is starting now.
Depending on the outcome,
it could turn into a criminal case.
Are you aware of that?
Yes, I'm aware.
I can't help but wonder.
All personnel transfers were frozen
but how did just one person
transfer to Korea?
On top of that
I heard a complaint
was filed against you.
Did you abandon a sinking ship
to save yourself?
I don't know
if you can't say anything
or if you're just choosing
to stay silent.
But I think it's possible
you're in league with the people
who embezzled from the China branch.
But...
We shouldn't assume anything
without evidence.
That's why I took you in.
Yes, ma'am.
There's only one thing
you can do here.
Work hard.
If the audit results are positive,
that's great news for you.
And even if they're negative
your hard work will still count
for something.
Do you get what I'm saying?
Yes, ma'am.
All right, you may go.
2 MONTHS AGO, CHINA
POINT OF CONTACT
TRADING COMPANY TRANSACTIONS
COPY TO USB DRIVE
Who's there?
CUSTOMER SERVICE MANUAL
What are you working on?
The documents Ms. Jang requested.
Are you putting them together
like this?
Is this not good enough?
No, you're doing great.
- Mr. Yang.
- Yes?
Mr. Gong, it's time for lunch.
Is it?
Let's go.
Come on, Ji-hye.
I'm not really hungry.
You two go ahead.
How can you work on an empty stomach?
Should I get you
a salad or something?
No, I'll be fine.
Enjoy your lunch.
Mr. Jeong hasn't come in yet?
No, and he's not answering his phone.
- Hello.
- Yes, hello.
- Good day.
CEO'S OFFICE
CEO JEONG SEON-HYUK
Yes?
Would you like some coffee, sir?
That would be lovely.
MANTUA, ITALY
Mr. Jeong.
Hi, Mr. Sponza.
I just got your invoice.
All is good. See?
I'll send everything out like that.
Thank you.
Did you get any call from Hongsung?
No.
But even if they did,
don't worry.
Okay.
I'll call you again soon.
I'll do everything I can
to set the mood.
- No, don't do anything.
- Yes, sir.
I'll handle Ms. Cha.
Don't worry.
She may seem easy to sway,
but she doesn't open up easily.
I'll lighten the mood somehow.
I'll do my best to back you up.
- Don't. Just stay put.
- Yes, sir. I'll stay put.
Let's give it our all today
and get the best managers
on our side.
ANTACID
You're having one too?
Because we're a team.
- Here they come.
- What?
- Don't be nervous.
- Yes, sir.
- Hey.
- Hello, ladies!
Let me take that for you.
We've been waiting forever
for you ladies.
- Right this way.
- Hello.
Hello.
- Have a seat right here.
- Hello.
When is Hongsung going to hire
some new people?
It's always the same faces.
All old and worn-out.
That's harsh, Ms. Cha.
I'm still in my twenties.
No, you're definitely not.
I swear I am.
No, I don't believe you.
- Just pour us some drinks.
- Thank you.
All right, give me your glasses.
Delicious, isn't it?
- Cheers!
Laknes?
Didn't they go out of business?
You've got it all wrong.
They strategically decided to wait
for the market to peak.
That's called going out of business.
It's true. They did.
But market trends
are always changing.
Now is the right time
for Laknes to make a comeback.
Exactly.
Fine, let's say
they went out of business.
They already failed once.
Would they try again without a plan?
They prepared thoroughly
for their comeback.
Being prepared is great and all
but Ms. Cha recently...
Can I tell them?
Of course not.
- I shouldn't.
- What is it?
So the thing is
she got an offer from a certain brand
to run their flagship store
in Seongsu-dong.
Habsburg?
How did you...
Of course, I know everything
that happens in this industry.
But that place is...
Sure, it's nice.
We can't stop you from going there.
Don't they offer managers
a 15% commission?
I'm sure that's true
for the first month.
But they'll lower it
after their opening month.
I already know.
How do you know?
Those punks always
pull the same scheme.
Ms. Cha.
I wasn't going to say this, but...
Sis.
You're really breaking my heart.
What?
Why are you so naive?
You've been played so many times,
but you still don't get it.
This isn't the first time
they've pulled this.
Why do you keep working with them
when they play you every time?
Why do you always turn us down
and choose to suffer
working with those punks?
I swear I'm not saying this
because you won't work with us.
How many years
have we known each other?
It just breaks my heart
to see you go through that!
Maybe you should stop drinking,
Mr. Yang.
Imagine she were your sister!
Sis.
Just promise me one thing.
I can't force you to work with us
but just don't let them hurt you.
Give it your best shot.
That's all I ask.
Damn, you almost got me.
That was so close.
I thought you were actually drunk.
- We've got a long way to go.
- Oh, my gosh.
- The night is young.
- Jeez.
- Cheers.
She's so smart
She's so charming
She drives me crazy
I like her so much...
Goodness.
Your glass is empty.
Let me pour you a drink.
I keep drinking,
but I wonder if it's poisoned.
No poison, just sincerity.
Pour me one too.
I can't deal with you, Mr. Yang.
That's too bad. Deal with it.
When we get the Laknes samples,
I'll save you a horsehair bag.
If you're giving me one,
make it alligator.
Alligator is nice too
but you haven't seen
their burgundy horsehair.
It's beautiful.
Horsehair or alligator,
it doesn't matter.
The timing couldn't be worse.
Why did it have to be now?
Do you think it'll work?
I don't know.
Goodness, how can you say that
when you came here to convince me?
I'll be honest with you, Ms. Cha.
I'm not sure about Laknes.
But with you,
I think we can make it work.
Well, aren't you a smooth talker?
Even if it's the same brand
there can be a huge gap in revenue
depending on the manager.
You know that yourself.
I wouldn't ask you
if I didn't believe in this brand.
If anyone could sell it,
then I'd ask anyone.
But this is something
only you can do.
Is that a good thing or a bad thing?
As for incentives and benefits
I'll match the highest
industry standards.
Let's give it a shot, Ms. Cha.
I'm getting played again.
Come on.
Have a drink.
Drink up.
I know you really need me
- You're too perfect
- I saw your eyes...
SINCHON SEOLLEONGTANG
Jeez, those chicks can really drink.
Why say that
after you had such a good time?
Sorry?
It's not right
to bad-mouth people
after having a good time with them.
We're the ones who need them.
Well...
I wasn't exactly bad-mouthing them.
It was more like
an expression of surprise.
Then just say
they can really hold their liquor.
Why are you calling them chicks
and saying they drink too much?
You've been sprouting up lately.
Should I nip that in the bud?
I'm sorry, sir.
- Mr. Yang.
- Thank you.
- Gi-tae.
- Yes, sir.
It's not just you, Gi-tae.
That's human nature.
Everyone's different
behind closed doors.
It's best to be careful.
Yes, sir. I'll keep that in mind.
Don't forget what I said,
even if you go to a new company.
Yes, sir.
Sorry?
So have you made a decision?
Are you leaving the company?
What?
Are you quitting, Park Gi-tae?
What? I mean...
What's with that guilty look?
You did nothing wrong.
I'm just curious.
The luck that passed me by
came together...
- Gi-tae, increase the echo.
- Okay.
It became you and came to me
In a rainstorm
I'll become...
Thank you for the offer, Mr. Gong.
Thank you for seeing me.
But why did you come yourself
this time?
Mr. Yang was always the one
who went drinking with us.
I thought you weren't on good terms
with your team.
I can't say that's entirely false.
Are things better now?
...I'll go anywhere
Trust in me now...
Yes, I'm working on it.
You should work a little harder.
Pardon?
You know Mr. Jeong
started his own business.
Did you know
he's been trying to scout people?
He's much more friendly now.
Really? Mr. Gong?
- Yes.
- No way.
Trust in me now
- Let's go, Laknes!
- Let's go!
I wasn't trying to hide it from you.
But I did get an offer
from Mr. Jeong.
Hey, you should've told us
right away.
I'm sorry, it's just...
I didn't know how to bring it up.
So the thing is...
How do I say this?
I'm not the only one
Mr. Jeong made an offer to.
What are you saying?
He made offers to employees
on other teams as well.
That seemed a bit problematic.
So I was trying to think
of a way to tell you.
As far as I know...
It's more than four people.
What exactly is he trying to do?
What did Ms. Park say?
What do you think?
I said I was quitting,
and she said okay.
Maybe she thought it was inevitable.
She might've even felt grateful.
Hey.
I have to move aside
so people like you
can move up the ladder.
If you resign, where will you go?
You're going to quit at 40
without a plan?
Does your wife know?
Of course, she does.
She told me to do whatever I want.
But she said she'd kill me
if I can't support the family.
Don't you have regrets?
Yes, I do.
Sometimes, I wonder
if I should've worked harder.
If I had
could I have been
a candidate for associate director?
That sort of thing.
Mr. Jeong.
If you just get through
this promotion cycle
I think you'll have a shot.
Hey.
You're skilled
and gaining good work experience,
so you might not know this.
But I wasn't promoted to team leader
based on my skills.
It was based on seniority.
Do you know the highest position
you can reach through seniority?
Team leader.
I'm a team leader.
It's over for me.
Aren't you thinking too negatively?
You're the best at this job.
What are you talking about?
Thanks for saying that.
Jeez.
Eun-tae.
Someday
if we ever meet again through work
I hope you won't be
too disappointed in me.
What are you saying?
I'm just saying.
I hope you don't feel that way.
INCOMING CALL
TEAM 4 MR. JEONG SEON-HYUK
ASSISTANT MANAGER GONG EUN-TAE
- Hello?
- Hey, Eun-tae.
Did you eat dinner?
Why are you doing this?
What are you referring to?
Not showing up to work
after resigning
or poaching employees?
Both, I suppose.
Well, once I thought about it
I realized I couldn't fake a smile
and say goodbye
when I'm betraying everyone.
That's why I haven't been to work.
And it's true that I made job offers.
They can make their own decisions.
So did you just call me
to ask if I had dinner?
So what is Hongsung going to do?
They'll have to punish me somehow.
What exactly are you expecting?
I'm sure you're not far off.
Is that right?
What about you?
Will you stay at Hongsung?
- What do you mean?
- Do you know
what they all say
when I offer them a job?
They thank me
for recognizing their worth.
Hongsung doesn't know
how to develop its employees.
I mean, they have a guy like you
caught up in office politics
and doing odd jobs.
So why don't you take this chance
to think about it?
I'll pretend we never had
this conversation.
HONGSUNG SALES DIVISION 1
TEAM LEADER JEONG SEON-HYUK
Eun-tae.
You're the reason I'm leaving.
I made this decision because of you.
All I did was find the courage
to do the job I'd been given.
I had no idea that courage
would lead to this result.
You see...
I think...
I'll become Hongsung's enemy.
You could say the one
who made him Hongsung's enemy...
was me.
- Good morning.
- Hello, Mr. Gong.
- Hello.
- Hello, sir.
Hello.
- You're here early, Ms. Jang.
- Hello, Mr. Gong.
Good morning, Mr. Gong.
What's going on between you two?
Look at this.
Didn't she do a great job?
Ji-hye worked very hard on it.
You didn't stay up all night
for this, did you?
Please tell me you didn't.
I'm sorry, Ms. Jang.
Tell me if anything is missing
or needs to be revised.
I'll fix it right away.
What I'm trying to say is...
Ji-hye.
Do you have the original file?
Yes, I shared it
on the company network.
That's great.
Let's use it as our team's manual.
Sorry?
I'm really sorry, Ji-hye.
I should have been clearer.
I was just asking
for a simple document
so I could begin working right away.
I wasn't asking you
to write a full report.
It's not like I'm a director.
I mean, this is flawless.
Even I can't make
something like this.
I was going to tell her,
but she was doing such a good job.
I wanted to see the final result...
Ji-hye?
I'm sorry.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
I bet you've never been up here.
No, I haven't.
I didn't even know
we had a place like this.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry
I didn't bring you here sooner
especially after you've been here
for over four months.
And as your team leader,
I didn't know how anxious you were.
I'm also sorry for that.
I loved seeing how hard you worked,
so I left you alone.
I had no clue it was out of anxiety.
You're a contract worker
who has just one year
to prove yourself
if you want to stay here.
It must be tough.
Well, I'm not the only one
in that position.
I can do a better job.
What exactly can you do better,
and how?
I'll be honest.
I can't tell you
to trust me and follow my lead,
or that hard work is all you need.
But instead
I'll do everything I can
to deliver results
starting with Laknes.
If the team gets good results,
I'll gain leverage as team leader.
Then I'll have the confidence
to advocate for you
because Sales Team 5 needs you,
no matter what.
What is this?
It's the file you worked on.
Keep it in your wallet.
Regardless of the outcome
it doesn't change your worth
as the person who made this.
Don't put your faith in the company.
Don't put your faith in me, either.
Trust in your own worth
as the creator of that file.
Thank you, Mr. Gong.
Stay up here a little longer.
Just don't stay here all day.
Mr. Gong.
If I become a full-time employee,
I'll treat you to a meal.
No.
I'll treat you.
I promise I'll buy you
something delicious!
Make it premium Korean beef.
All right.
I'm sorry, Mr. Gong.
I should've made
my instructions clearer.
It was ultimately my mistake.
Don't worry about it.
Mr. Gong.
I'm sure you have
many questions for me.
Why haven't you asked me anything?
If you had something to tell me,
you would've already.
The fact that you haven't
means you're not ready yet.
It wasn't an easy decision for me.
Please just know that.
How many people in total?
Five, as far as we can tell.
Team 1's Park Jin-u,
Team 2's Choi Ju-hui
Team 3's Kang Yeong-seo,
Team 5's Park Gi-tae
and Team 4's Oh Jeong-hyeon.
He tried to completely
dismantle Team 4.
- Mr. Oh.
- Yes, ma'am.
I rejected him right away.
Mr. Jeong didn't clock in
today, either?
He also stopped taking our calls
since yesterday.
I did some digging.
He appears to be mainly importing
gray market products from Mantua.
It seems he established contacts
in Mantua before he quit.
He's also already taken
Safilo and Philipp Plein...
Were you aware?
Their sales figures were poor.
It's been a while since they were
mentioned at the meetings.
Why didn't you stop him?
I figured I'd let him have that much.
I couldn't promote him, anyway.
And he needed to find his own path.
But poaching our people is
taking it too far.
- I think...
- Mr. Jang.
Yes, ma'am.
What are your thoughts?
MULTI-BRAND SHOE STORE
PROJECT PROPOSAL
What is this?
A project proposal
for a multi-brand shoe store?
What if we used this
to put some pressure on Mr. Jeong?
Tell me.
Do you want to take this on?
I'd like the company to take it on.
If you propose this
as associate director
it won't just be Team 5's project.
It'll become the entire
Sales Division's project.
We have to break into this market
at some point, anyway.
Even if we sue Mr. Jeong,
we won't gain anything.
And filing a claim against
our Mantua partners will be useless.
"We had no idea.
What do you expect us to do?"
They'll feign ignorance.
And, to be frank...
we can't stop our employees
from wanting to leave.
So I propose
that we take all of Mantua back.
You want to use the shoe supply
to put pressure on Mantua?
Mr. Jeong gets his entire supply
from Mantua.
So I suggest we become a client
Mantua can't afford to lose.
So big that Mr. Jeong can't compete.
We'll put in a supply order
and cut off
Mr. Jeong's entire supply.
Whose idea was this?
It was Mr. Gong's.
Mr. Gong.
Why a multi-brand shoe store?
With clothing or accessories
we also have to worry about hangers,
displays, props, and more.
The downside to shoes is
that the boxes are bulky.
But they're easy to manage
and require less preparation.
There's also less inventory per store
and, after each season
we can send leftovers to outlets,
which is an advantage.
I believe it's a good project.
Are you almost done
prepping the Laknes launch?
Ms. Park.
I came up with this project
but it doesn't mean
only I can take it on.
Even if you give it to another team,
I'll do my best to help out.
Just answer the question.
Yes.
Construction of the store's interior
is complete.
We've also recruited managers.
So can you take this on?
Yes, I can.
- Mr. Jang.
- Yes, ma'am.
Schedule a meeting
with the Finance Team.
- Mr. Gong, resubmit your proposal.
- Yes, ma'am.
- And get ready for a trip to Mantua.
- Okay.
Goodbye, ma'am.
Eun-tae.
You should pace yourself.
At this rate,
you'll leave the rest of us behind.
He's right. If you're going to do
the multi-brand shoe store
you should give us
some of your other brands.
Okay, I'll discuss it with Mr. Jang.
Yes, talk it over
and help Mr. Kim out.
What?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Sorry?
Who are you to tell him
to help me out?
Why would I take anything
from a junior colleague?
I mean...
Weren't you planning on
taking some of his brands?
Why are you pretending?
Look at this bastard.
Then what about you?
Are you whining
because you couldn't even get scraps?
"Whining"?
Are you serious?
You're the one
snooping around a junior's team
looking for scraps to take.
Has this bastard lost his mind?
Do you want to fight?
Don't call me a bastard.
We're both team leaders.
How dare you call me that?
What are you, an associate director?
Hey!
What a great example you're setting
as team leaders.
Why don't you get back to work
instead of fighting?
Cut the nonsense.
At a company, one person's decision
inevitably affects others.
Everyone here is
both a cause and an effect
of one another.
THE ORDINARY JACKPOT
2,034,320 WON SENT TO LEE JI-HYE
FROM HONGSUNG INTERNATIONAL
Hello.
Yes, hello.
- How much is this?
- It's 32,000 won.
Could you give me a discount?
Hi, ladies.
Can I help you find something?
- This is so pretty.
- This?
If you like it...
Excuse me, do you have that brown one
in another color?
That's the last one we have.
- How much is this?
- It's 60,000 won.
All right, thank you.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
May I try this on?
Thank you.
It looks great on you.
- Do you think so?
- Yeah.
- That one doesn't look good.
- Right?
That one's so pretty on you.
You should get it.
Thank you.
She said that when we first met.
"Get me baseline margins
for the brands we're in charge of.
Customer prices,
customer service manuals..."
You have no idea, right?
But that's not all.
Credit memo logs,
invoice checklists...
She asked me to prepare all of that.
But do you know what's really crazy?
I memorized it all in one shot.
Isn't it?
You know I'm bad at memorization.
Remember when I ran into my ex
on the street
and stuttered like crazy
because I forgot his name?
I don't know. I still don't remember.
But I memorized all of that
in one shot.
Isn't that amazing?
But you can't just memorize
the words.
There's a logical sequence
based on the workflow.
That's how I memorized it.
Can you imagine how nervous I was?
That assistant manager has
such a strong aura.
She looks at you
like she's studying you.
Like a customs officer
looking you over.
So imagine how hard I worked.
I even lost my appetite.
So when I brought her the file,
do you know what she said...
Yes, what is it?
Your boyfriend came?
Okay, let's talk later.
Bye.
But this is the highlight.
She said I did a great job.
Darn it.
Whatever, I did great.
Subtitles by Eunice Kim